Lesson 6. Susan stays home and bakes cookies. Susan decides to cheer up her husband. Bob
loves her homemade cookies. Nicole suggests she start a cookie business.
Bob, I baked cookies for you. That was so nice of you, dear. You've got a heart of gold.
Go ahead and pick out. These are delicious. I thought they might cheer you up. You've been
in a bad mood lately. I guess I have been a little on edge, but these cookies are just what
the doctor ordered. Do I smell cookies? Yes, Nicole. Help yourself. Yum, yum. These are
out of this world. You could go into business selling these. You could call them Susan
scrumptious cookies. You'd make a bundle. Good thinking. Don't forget to give me credit
for the idea after you're rich and famous. You know I always give credit where credit is
due.